[{"answer": "Don't call him a dipshit", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "And you don't.  What's she doing in there", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Like what? The moons of Jupiter", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't want to have any conversation", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " You're like this fly, buzzing buzzing everywhere", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": " This play", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Sometimes I come here and just scan the heavens", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Looking for something", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The Bible. Why should I read a bunch of dumb stories about some ancient guy who supposedly worked miracles", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Your father doesn't like me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " 'Then why don't you talk to her?", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " 'She'll sure think the same if I do it. You're her father and comes a time when a father's gotta mention.", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "You don't know the first thing about being someone's friend", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "You don't know what you want", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "New paint. Extra chrome. Not a scratch anywhere", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Reconditioned. Completely. Be a collector's someday. Twelve hundred", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Where did you get", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I didn't say you did", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " She great or what", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No.  But are you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I care for her", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I wouldn't do that", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We didn't tell him any different for years", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Since I was five. My mom's a cocktail waitress", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You and the Carter boy. Want to catch me up on recent developments", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I'm asking how much", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I should have told you sooner", "docId": "Walk-to-Remember_-A.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No. The drugs just stopped working. If anything, doing things I love kept me healthy longer", "qsentId": 28}]